<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: personal | redperadot]]></title>
  <link href="http://redperadot.github.io/blog/categories/personal/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://redperadot.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2013-06-24T01:02:14-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://redperadot.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Cody Hannafon]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's With the Name]]></title>
    <link href="http://redperadot.github.io/blog/2013/06/21/whats-with-the-name/"/>
    <updated>2013-06-21T10:47:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://redperadot.github.io/blog/2013/06/21/whats-with-the-name</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Redperadot as you could&rsquo;ve guessed is just the color red with the stone peridot, and yes I know I spell and pronounce it wrong. There&rsquo;s a simple reason. When I was eight I got my first email.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Exiting for a eight year old in the early 2000&rsquo;s. My mom sat me down at our old beige computer and told me about email, how you could send a letter from the computer and have it reach the other side of the world within minutes. Then told me I could have my very own for free. My eyes lit up and she told me I needed a username. We sat there thinking of one she thought my birthstone and I being eight thought of my favorite color at the time blue, together that made <a href="&#x6d;&#97;&#105;&#108;&#x74;&#x6f;&#x3a;&#x62;&#x6c;&#x75;&#101;&#x70;&#101;&#114;&#x61;&#x64;&#111;&#116;&#x40;&#x79;&#x61;&#x68;&#x6f;&#x6f;&#x2e;&#99;&#x6f;&#109;">&#x62;&#x6c;&#117;&#x65;&#x70;&#101;&#x72;&#97;&#x64;&#111;&#116;&#64;&#x79;&#97;&#104;&#x6f;&#x6f;&#x2e;&#x63;&#x6f;&#109;</a> (long gone) and being eight I miss heard how my mother spelt it and typed it in peradot instead of peridot. Well it worked out, no one else had it.</p>

<p>When I was around fifteen I decided I needed an upgrade and started using gmail and at the time I was going through that dark clothed no one likes me stage that all fifteenth year olds go through, so my favorite color was red. Ever since I&rsquo;ve been using the handle redperadot as my main username, but now I use all sorts of others goldperadot for admin stuff, blackperadot for work things, blueperadot for education, and a few more. As for pronunciation I&rsquo;m just american and ignorant.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Start of Something]]></title>
    <link href="http://redperadot.github.io/blog/2013/06/21/the-start-of-something/"/>
    <updated>2013-06-21T08:39:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://redperadot.github.io/blog/2013/06/21/the-start-of-something</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Well, this is my first post, let&rsquo;s see if I keep it up. I&rsquo;ve always wanted to keep a record of my thoughts and knowledge but have always been paranoid of who will get this information. Why am I paranoid you ask, or even better why have I decided to do such a thing in the first place? Well, I don&rsquo;t really know. I&rsquo;ve always been one to make split decisions that make no sense, or maybe its just that the world could use another somebody to spill their thoughts (for some reason), it could even be it will make me a better person less&hellip; antisocial if you could call me that. Either way here we are.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>We I do have a reason to be paranoid on the internet. With all the hard to read terms of service and whatnot. When you post something on Facebook, Twitter, or Tumblr do you still own it? When you receive an email on Gmail, AOL, or Yahoo is it not looked through to have ads targeted on you like a bomber? This is why I&rsquo;m paranoid, because everything you do on the internet is studied and collected to be used by corporation for whatever reason. Don&rsquo;t get me wrong sometimes it necessary but at the extent that its happens, I just don&rsquo;t want to be apart of it. So I make it one of my mission to understand how it all works, to better know how not to have my art, my thoughts, my content taken from me just because I didn&rsquo;t read some fine print or I didn&rsquo;t know they had no right to take it from me in the first place.</p>

<p>Look at me go on with my craziness; I blame my mother, long enough around her and you start to become a conspirator. Anyway sit down and let me tell you about myself. I can be a bit forgetful at times (or a lot) so if you find me repeating myself or if you have any questions, comments, things of that nature you can drop a line in the disqus form and or also get me at my email <a href="&#109;&#97;&#x69;&#x6c;&#116;&#x6f;&#x3a;&#114;&#101;&#x64;&#112;&#x65;&#x72;&#x61;&#x64;&#x6f;&#116;&#x40;&#100;&#97;&#x72;&#x6b;&#x67;&#101;&#x6d;&#x2e;&#x6e;&#101;&#116;&#46;">&#114;&#101;&#100;&#112;&#101;&#114;&#x61;&#x64;&#x6f;&#x74;&#64;&#x64;&#x61;&#114;&#107;&#103;&#x65;&#109;&#x2e;&#110;&#101;&#x74;&#x2e;</a> Thank god they found a cure for alzheimer&rsquo;s just in case it&rsquo;s early onset. Besides the alzheimer&rsquo;s I&rsquo;m also a graphic designer, IT something or another, and web programmer hence the fabulous site. These skills come from the people I work, live, and hang with every day and for that I appreciate them very much.</p>

<p>Even if no one reads this blog I think I&rsquo;m still going to post to it, to keep a memory of me in the world long after I&rsquo;m gone. Its also nice to look back to see what I was like in the past, how I have change for good or for worse. So this project is for me more than anyone else and I&rsquo;m OK if its just a journal, but it you would like to read along thanks and I hope you have fun just as much as I am.</p>

<p>See you later,</p>

<p>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cody Hannafon (redperadot)</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
